learnamericanenglishonline.com 2018-12-27

# privacy policy

LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com Privacy Statement

A friendly reminder from your teacher: 

Your privacy is extremely important. LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com has created this privacy statement ("Statement") in order to demonstrate our commitment to customer privacy. Privacy on the LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com web site (the "Site") is of great importance to us. Because we gather important information from our visitors and customers, we have established this Statement as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices. We reserve the right to change this Statement at any time, so please visit LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com regularly to review our privacy statement.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact the operator of this website at [paul@learnamericanenglishonline.com](mailto:paul@learnamericanenglishonline.com) and enter the words "privacy concerns" in the subject field. 

Because LearnAmericanEnglishOnline works in partnership with Ezoic, an artificial intelligence platform for pubishers, here is an additional link for [the privacy policy to which LAEO Incorporated and Ezoic both agree](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/learnamericanenglishonline.com). 

Collected Information

Learn American English Online is committed to keeping information gathered from subscribers strictly confidential. Email addresses will not be sold or shared with anyone. Also, as a Google publisher, Learn American English Online.com wants you to know that Google uses cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process. 

We use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyze our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. 

Subscriber email addresses and any personal information will not be distributed or shared with third parties. Subscribers are also asked to provide an email address when registering for the Service, in order to receive updates, lessons, and newsletters. 

In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services (including registration), we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, experience with our products and services, and more detailed contact preferences. Subscribers and visitors always have the option of choosing not to provide us with this information.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

This website uses Google Analytics to collect data from visitors. To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, you may install this [Opt-out Browser Addon](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

HTML eMail

LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com practice is to include web beacons in HTML-formatted email messages (messages that include graphics) that LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com, or its agents, sends in order to determine which email messages were opened and to note whether a message was acted upon.

In general, any file served as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon. LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com may also include web beacons from other companies within pages served by LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com so that LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com advertisers may receive auditing, and reporting.

Log Files

LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com maintains log files of the traffic that visits our site. We do not link any information gathered in these log files to personally identifying information. Log files are used to manage traffic loads and information technology requirements for providing reliable service. Information collected includes IP addresses and browser types.

Information Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

All information gathered on the site is stored and maintained in secure facilities that limit access to authorized personnel only.

Retention of Information

LearnAmericanEnglishOnline.com will keep personal information of its users for as long as they are registered subscribers or users of our products and services, and for a reasonable time thereafter.

Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

Change in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

Contact 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us by emailing paul@learnamericanenglishonline.com. In the subject field, enter the words "privacy concerns."
